about just how accurate are the memories that we know are true, that we believe in? There is decades of research, examples and examples of cases like this, where individuals really, really believe. None of those teenagers who identified him thought that they were picking the wrong person. None of them thought they couldn't see the person's face. We all have to be very careful. All our memories are reconstructed memories. They are the product of what we originally experienced and everything that's happened afterwards. They're dynamic. They're malleable. They're volatile, and as a result, we all need to remember to be cautious, that the accuracy of our memories is not measured in how vivid they are nor how certain you are that they're correct. Thank you. (Applause)
acerca de la exactitud de los recuerdos qué sabemos que son ciertos. Hay décadas de investigación, ejemplos y ejemplos de casos como éste, donde los individuos realmente creen. Ninguno de esos adolescentes que lo identificó pensaban que señalaban a la persona equivocada. Ninguno de ellos pensó que no podía ver la cara de la persona. Todos tenemos que ser muy cuidadosos. Todos nuestros recuerdos son recuerdos reconstruidos. Son el producto de lo que originalmente hemos vivido y de todo lo que pasó después. Son dinámicos. Son maleables. Son volátiles, y como resultado de ello, todos tenemos que recordar ser cautelosos, que la precisión de nuestros recuerdos no se mide en la forma en que están vivos ni en la certeza que tenemos de que son correctos. Gracias. (Aplausos)